<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Neurodiversity on Laura Anthony - Speaker &amp; Neuroinclusive Leader</title>
    <link>http://localhost:8080/tags/neurodiversity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Neurodiversity on Laura Anthony - Speaker &amp; Neuroinclusive Leader</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 08:39:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:8080/tags/neurodiversity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Equity in Inquiry</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/talks/equity-in-inquiry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 08:39:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/talks/equity-in-inquiry/</guid>
      <description>HR professionals and leaders conduct countless interviews for hiring, workplace investigations and performance evaluations. Yet, traditional interview techniques can disadvantage those who are neurodivergent, leading to missed opportunities and flawed outcomes. With 1 in 5 people identifying as neurodivergent and with neurodiversity becoming a strategic asset for organizations, HR professionals need to learn how conduct interviews in ways that work for all communication and cognitive styles. This session teaches practical strategies to adapt traditional approaches and helps leaders understand how inclusive interviewing can improve their talent and investigation practices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Different Wiring, Shared Solutions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/talks/different-wiring-shared-solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 08:38:30 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/talks/different-wiring-shared-solutions/</guid>
      <description>Conflict is inevitable, and the stress it creates can be particularly challenging for neurodivergent individuals who process emotions, interpret communication, and respond to tension in different ways. For dispute resolution professionals, like mediators and arbitrators, as well as workplace leaders, it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand these differences and how traditional ADR practices can create barriers to resolution. This training offers practitioners insight on how to eliminate these barriers, implement inclusive practices that account for diverse thinking and communication styles and achieve better solutions for all parties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Leadership Mindset for All Minds</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/talks/leadership-mindset-for-all-minds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 08:38:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/talks/leadership-mindset-for-all-minds/</guid>
      <description>Leadership is evolving and one of the most transformative shifts is the recognition and leveraging of neurodiversity within teams. This session equips team leaders to foster neuroinclusion in talent acquisition and development, moving beyond accommodations to systems where all minds thrive. By understanding how we think and communicate differently, attendees will learn to how be an inclusive leader, reduce bias and build collaborative teams where neurodiversity drives innovation and growth. This isn&amp;rsquo;t just a talk about inclusion—it&amp;rsquo;s a practical roadmap to help leaders innovate and harness their team&amp;rsquo;s full potential.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great Minds Don&#39;t Think Alike</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/talks/great-minds-dont-think-alike/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 08:37:50 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/talks/great-minds-dont-think-alike/</guid>
      <description>As AI and automation shift talent needs, skills like creativity, innovation and complex problem solving are becoming more critical. And these skills are exactly where neurodivergent talent excel. With up to 20% of the workforce identifying as neurodivergent, smart organizations are moving beyond inclusion to harnessing these cognitive differences as competitive advantages. This session equips leaders with practical tools to recognize, develop and leverage the unique strengths of their neurodiverse talent. Because embracing neurodiversity isn&amp;rsquo;t just the right thing to do—it&amp;rsquo;s a powerful differentiator in an AI-dominated future.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
